What are you?
Oh, I'm OK.
I will be.
I said she could stay with us, Mum.
I just thought she feels better.
Yeah.
Of course she can.
Oh, this won't be for long.
Well, you can stay as long as you want my love.
You really missed you.
Pops.
Great to see you, love.
Oh.
All right, shall we get you off to bed then?
You should have given me some warm.
I'll have to put the electric blanket on.
Sorry.
All right, Della.
Freezing up there.
In a bedroom, Peter unpacks her suitcase.
The middle-aged woman opens her green case.
Do you want, yeah, PJs?
Yeah.
Lifting a bundle of pajamas, Peter finds a sheet of paper labeled Lancaster North Hospital Discharged Sheet.
He closes the suitcase and brings glory to the pajamas.
There you go.
Thank you.
He picks up the locket.
He kept it.
Oh, of course.